But the Sunnah is that wear
the
ring on your small finger.
As for the first finger,
the second
finger, and the ring finger,
the ulama prohibit it.
And there are reports
regarding that from
the
Sunnah too, especially for
the first finger
and the middle finger.
The ring finger,
that's a prohibition from the
scholars because
they connect it to At-Tasha
Buhubi Kufar,
behaving like Kufar, who
choose wearing rings
to be on the ring finger,
because they believe that
that connects the heart from
that finger.
So when you put a ring on
it during marriage,
the ring helps you to sustain
your
marriage. So we avoid that.
They do it for worship.
We avoid
behaving like them. So that
who sees
us does not think that we
also
have that belief they have.
So don't put rings on your
first
three fingers, the first
finger,
the middle finger,
and the ring finger.
You can put your ring on the
thumb, but the Sunnah is that
you
have your ring
on the small finger.
For men, as for women,
put the ring wherever you
want.
If you like,